Borns Jewish Studies Program records, 1972-2010 C407
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1972-2009; undated (Box 5)
  - Hava Tirosh-Samuelson's AJS Paper December 1998, January-March 1999 (Box 6)
  - Travel information and brochures, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Two Covenant Theology, 1972-1980 (Box 6)
  - United Way Materials, 1994-2004 (Box 6)
  - Yiddish, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Yiddish, 1999-2001 (Box 6)
  - National Yiddish Book Center, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Yom HaShoah, 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - ZBT Incident, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Restricted files (Box 6)
- Multimedia, 1978-1984; undated (Box 7)
  - Audio Reels, 1975-1986
    - Fackenheim, B05404, 4-6-76 (Box 7)
    - Jewish Studies Conference, Reel 1, B04387, 3-16-1975 (Box 7)
    - Jewish Studies Conference, Reel 2, B04387, 3-16-1975 (Box 7)
    - Jewish Studies Conference, Reel 1, B04387, 3-17-1975 (Box 7)
    - Jewish Studies Conference, Reel 2, B04387, 3-17-1975 (Box 7)
    - Jewish Studies Lecture, C03674, 11-2-83 (Box 7)
    - Jewish Studies Annual Lecture, Bernard Lewis, Guest Lecturer, March 6, 1980 (Box 7)
    - George Stalmitz Lecture, Reel 1B06332, Elie Wiesel, Responses to Catastrophe: Jewish Rebirth in the Age of Yohanan ben Zakkai and Today, March 16, 1977 (Box 7)
    - George Stalmitz Lecture, Reel 2B06332, Elie Wiesel, Responses to Catastrophe: Jewish Rebirth in the Age of Yohanan ben Zakkai and Today, March 16, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Songs of Jerusalem and Myself: A Poetry Reading by Yehuda Amachai Reel 1, Elly Selnick Stolnitz Memorial Program, 1979; (program in box with reel) (Box 7)
    - Yehuda Amachai, Reel 2 (Box 7)
    - W. Gunther Plaut, 6633, 11-17-1986 (Box 7)
    - Jewish Studies Lecture, 11-3-1983 (Box 7)
    - Yigael Yade, C03G72, 11-3-1983 (Box 7)
    - Stolnitz Lecture, Cynthia Ozick, 4-12-1972 (Box 7)
  - Cassettes, 1983-2002
    - JSP 25th Anniversary Gala Brave Old World Tape 2, May 2, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Career Night Talk, 1998 (Box 7)
    - John Efron Jews & the God of Science 1993 New Institute, 4/23/1993 (Box 7)
    - Block Lecture Emil Facknheim, 3/30/1992 (Box 7)
    - Emil Fackenheim Session 1 New Institute, 3/27/92 (Box 7)
    - Emil Fackenheim New Institute Session 5, 3/28/92 (Box 7)
    - Discussion between an Auschwitz survivor and a former Nazi youth leader, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Alvin Rosenfeld The Image of Anne Frank Radio 100 Amsterdam, April 7, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Session 6 New Institute, 3/29/92 (Box 7)
    - , New Institute Neal Rosenblatl-vocal, David Lyons-piano, Jewish Music, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Polish Rail Car Weekend Edition, 7/8/89 (Box 7)
    - Amichai, Oehuda, 11/1/95 (Box 7)
      (side be labeled, "Not Amichai, tape didn't work)
    - Opening of Anne Frank- Exhibition, II (Box 7)
    - Opening of Anne Frank Exhibit in HamburgI, Aug. 31, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Schumacher and Dzigan: A Series of Yiddish Tapes, (5 tapes) (Box 7)
    - David Sorkin Whose Bible is it Anyway Bronstein Lecture, March 4, 1993 (Box 7)
    - 1998 Bronstein Lecture, Egon Mayer The Fears of the Faithful: Are American Jews Destined to Vanish?, 10/29/1998 (Box 7)
    - 1998 Bronstein Lecture, Egon Mayer The Fears of the Faithful: Are American Jews Destined to Vanish?, 10/29/1998 (Box 7)
    - Susannah Heschel Transforming Jesus from Rabbi to Aryan Bronstein Lecture, Hillel, 10/11/95 (Box 7)
    - Omer Bartov Jew in Cinema: Perpetrator & Victim, 4/10/02 (Box 7)
    - Prof. Geoffrey Hartman Learning from Survivors, 9 Nov. 1994 (Box 7)
    - Helen & Martin Schwartz Lecture, Geoffrey Hartman Reading the Wound: on Holocaust Testimony, Art, and Trauma, 10 Nov. 1994 (Box 7)
    - Jim Ackerman Sinai or Zion? Where is God in the Hebrew Bible April 24, New Institute, 1993; (2 tapes) (Box 7)
    - Brave Old World Tape 1JSP 25th Anniversary Gala, May 2, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Amir Eshel- Paul Celan's Poethics of the Other, 9/20/00 (Box 8)
    - Zvi Lederman Stones, Shards, & Computers: Understanding Cultural Changes Through Biblical Archaeology, Nov. 12, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Ilan Avisan, 10/30/00 (Box 8)
    - Putnam, Hilary Levina's Challenge, 12/2/99 (Box 8)
    - Putnam, Hilary Rosenweig & Wittgenstein, 12/1/99 (Box 8)
    - Through the Looking Glass: Women in the Exodus Narrative 1999 Simona & Hart Hasten Visiting Fellows Program, Dr. Avivah Gottlieb Zornberg, April 15, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Ilan Avisan, undated (Box 8)
    - Michael Brocke, 10/88 (Box 8)
    - Omer Bartov-Schwartz lecture Jewish Cinema: Hero & Anti-Hero, 4/21/02 (Box 8)
    - Interview w/ Gulie Ne'eman Arad, 12/7/95 (Box 8)
    - David Mersky, JS Career Night, 10/26/00 (Box 8)
    - Elisheva Carlebach-Bronstein Lecture in JS Revealing the Secrets of Judaism: Jewish Life in Christian Eyes, November 13, 2000 (Box 8)
    - PROFILE 91:01, Post-it 5-23-91 Shoshana- For your archives. This tape is of PROFILE, a radio program where Alvin spoke on Israel's attitude to the Persian Gulf Crisis. Patsy (Box 8)
    - PROFILE 91-33 (Box 8)
    - Haua Tiresh-Rothschild Session 3 Jewish Women & the Renewal of American Jewry, 3/28/92 (Box 8)
    - Saul FriedländerHist., Mem., and Jewish Continuity after the Holoc., 10/1/84 (Box 8)
    - Derek Penslar Jewish Philanthropy & Jewish Community New Inst. Session 4, 3/28/92 (Box 8)
    - Saul Friedländer History, Memory, and Jewish Continuity…, 10/1/1984 (Box 8)
    - Saul Friedländer Present-Day Historiographical Controversies Concerning Nazi Policies Toward the Jews, 10/8/1984; (3 tapes) (Box 8)
    - Yigael Yadin Masada No. 1, 11-2-83 (Box 8)
    - Yigael Yadin Masada No. 2, 11-2-83 (Box 8)
    - Yigael Yadin Temple Scroll II No. 2, 11-2-83 (Box 8)
    - Conceptions and Misconceptions of the Holocaust 1984 Lilly Seminar, Sep. 22-23, 1984; (2 tapes) (Box 8)
    - Saul Friedländer The New Discourse on Nazism, 9-20-1984; (3 tapes) (Box 8)
    - Saul Friedländer History, Memory, and Jewish Continuity after the Holocaust, 10-1-1984; (2 tapes) (Box 8)
    - Yigael Yadin Hazor & Megiddo, 11-3-83 (Box 8)
    - A.D.L. Commission Meeting Baptist Joint Committee on Public Affairs, Dr. James Dunn, Jr. Executive Director, June 4, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Amos Oz Israel through its Literature, 10-25-2001 (Box 8)
    - Amos Oz Israel: Peace & War, 10-29-2001 (Box 8)
    - Alan Bern WFHB 91.3 FM Conversations w/ Debra Kent (Box 8)
    - Hilberg lecture Reflections on the Holocaust, 1-23-83 (Box 8)
    - Paula Hyman 1984 Piser Lecture, 11-5-1984 (Box 8)
    - Conor Cruise O'Brien The Zionist Experience AO0176, 3-24-1988 (Box 8)
    - Conor Cruise O'Brien Arab-Israeli Relations Today AO0177, 3-30-1988 (Box 8)
    - Conor Cruise O'Brien Roots of Zionism: Religion and Nationalism AO0175, 3-22-1988 (Box 8)
    - Conor Cruise O'Brien, 3-30-1988 (Box 8)
    - Dan Segre's Block Lecture AO0614, 3-27-1989 (Box 8)
    - Ruth Wisse (Hasten), The NY Intellectuals & the Jewish Question, 4-7-92 (Box 8)
    - Ruth Wisse, Hasten lecture, 4-6-92 (Box 8)
    - Michael Walzer Block Lecture, Biblical Wisdom: The Valor and Limits of Prudence in Political Life, 10-26-92 (Box 8)
    - Antony Polonsky Bronstein lecture, 2-17-92 (Box 8)
    - Antony Polonsky Bronstein lecture, 2-19-92 (Box 8)
    - Unlabeled, (2 tapes) (Box 8)
    - Avivah Gottlieb Zornberg Cries and Whispers: The Death of Sarah, Nov. 14, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Shulamit Volkov Block Lecture, 1996; (2 tapes) (Box 8)
    - Arnie Eisen, Exodus: History, Faith, & Covenant JSP Schwartz lecture 2, Oct 22, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Arnie Eisen Good Faith Solotkin/Friends Gathering, Oct 23, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Dieter Lamping The Representation of Jews in Post-War German Literature Paul Lecture, Bloomington, 9-16-97 (Box 8)
    - Today's Germany & the Jews IHC Indianapolis Paul Lecture, 9-14-97 (Box 8)
    - Ezra Mendelsohn Art & Jewish History Block Lecture, 9-22-97 (Box 8)
    - Tikva Frymer-Kensky, Bronstein Lecture Victims, Victors, & Virgins: Reading the Women of the Bible, Feb. 10, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Ronnie Hsia, Bronstein Lecture Between the Messiah & the Millennium: Jewish-Christian Relations in Central Europe, 5th to 18th Centuries, 12-1-97 (Box 8)
    - David Roskies, H & M Schwartz The Search for a Usable Jewish Past, 3-23-98 (Box 8)
    - David Roskies, H & M Schwartz The Golden Peacock in America IU JSP, 3-24-98 (Box 8)
    - Samuel D. Kassow The Rise of the Jewish Metropolis: Warsaw in the Modern Era Schwartz Lecture in JS, 11-17-98; (3 tapes) (Box 8)
    - Samuel D. Kassow, 2nd Schwartz Lecture in JS Resistance & History in the Warsaw Ghetto, 11-18-98; (3 tapes) (Box 8)
    - Primo Levi Alvin's Class at IU, 4-23-85 (Box 9)
    - Primo Levi, 4-23-85 (Box 9)
    - An Evening of Jewish Music, 3-10-87 (Box 9)
    - Holocaust Class in San Diego, 5/81, Mrs. Waterford/Mr. Hecht (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled tape (Box 9)
    - Aron Rodrigue, Nov. 6, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Yehuda Z. Blum The Juridical Status of Jerusalem Hasten Lecture, Feb. 15, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Yehuda Z. Blum From Camp David to Oslo Hasten Lecture, Feb. 16, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Abba Eban Reflection on WWII Circle Theatre, Indianapolis, 5-7-95 (Box 9)
    - Gertrud Koch, Paul Lecture The Return of the Past: Jewish Characters in Post – War German Film, Sept. 11, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Francis E. Peters Present at the Creation: Judaism & the Origins of Islam Bronstein Lecture, 10-1-1994 (Box 9)
    - Gilman Sander, 20 Marks or the Visible, Invisibility of Jews in contemp German Culture, H & M Schwartz Lecture, November 3, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Gilman Sander 20 The Jewish Body & the Jewish Mind: Reflections of the Gendering of Contemp. Jewish Culture in Germany H & M Schwartz Lecture II, November 4, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Julius Lester Blacks & Jews Bronstein Lecture, November 11, 1993 (Box 9)
    - The Impact of the Holocaust on Religious Thought Lilly Seminar, 1984; (Lilly Seminar Tape 3) (Box 9)
    - Popular Conceptions of the Holocaust Fackenheim (1), J985 Fackenheim/Eckhardt Mini Seminar, 1985 (Box 9)
    - The Impact of the Holocaust on Religious Thought Lilly Seminar, 1984; (Lilly Seminar Tape 4) (Box 9)
    - …National Monument Building of the Holocaust… Lilly Seminar, 1984; (Lilly Seminar Tape 5) (Box 9)
    - Popular Conceptions of the Holocaust Roy Eckhardt/Michael Morgan (4), J985 Mini Seminar, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Popular Conceptions of the Holocaust Eckhardt (2), J985 Fackenheim/Eckhardt Mini Seminar, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Popular Conceptions of the Holocaust Eckhardt (3), J985 Fackenheim/Eckhardt Mini Seminar, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Fackenheim/Hasten Fellow 1985 1st Lecture The Jewish Religious Situation Today, Sept. 19th (Box 9)
    - Fackenheim/Hasten Fellow 1985 2nd Lecture The Jew of Today and the Jewish Bible, Oct. 4th (Box 9)
    - Fackenheim/Hasten Fellow 1985 3rd Lecture Of Last Things: The Messianic Hope and the World to Come, Oct. 15th (Box 9)
    - W. Gunther Plaut, 11-17-86 (Box 9)
    - Elie Wiesel, 6448, 9-23-86 (Box 9)
    - Elie Wiesel, 6449, Lecture on Rabbi Akiva, 9-24-86 (Box 9)
    - Elie Wiesel, 6450, Lecture on Hasidic Masters, 9-25-86 (Box 9)
    - Elie Wiesel, 6450, Lecture on Hasidic Masters, 9-25-86 (Box 9)
    - Julius Lester Blacks & Jews Bronstein Lecture, November 11, 1993 (Box 9)
      (See box 3)
    - Israel Bartal Warriors or Cowards? Images of the Soldier in East Europe 1772-1914, Feb. 29, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Nicholas de Lange Jews and Greeks: Language & Identity in the Byzantine Empire, 4-2-97 (Box 9)
    - Hava Tirosh-Rothschild Created in His Image: The Divine & Human in Medieval Judaism New Institute, April 24, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Shaye CohenBlock Lecture, Uncircumcised Jews: Are Jewish Women Part of the Covenant?, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Proposal of Jewish Community Summer Schools in Israel, (Microcassette) (Box 9)
    - Fackenheim '82 Sacred Texts (Box 9)
    - Fachenheim (Box 9)
    - David Tracy (Box 9)
    - A: Bloom, B. Bloom & Cook 1 (Box 9)
    - A: Cook and Clark William, B: Williamson (Box 9)
    - Williamson (Box 9)
    - A: Gaston, B: Gaston/Greenberg (Box 9)
    - Greenberg (Box 9)
    - First Session (Box 9)
  - DVDs, 2003-2006 (Box 10)
    - April 2003 (Box 10)
      - Tape 5 & 6, Smelenski Tape 5 and Shapiro Tape 1-2, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 7 & 8, Shapiro Tape 3 and Braverman Tape 1-2 (Box 10)
      - Tape 9 & 10, Braverman Tape 3-4, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 11 & 12, Braverman Tape 5, Melameo, and Zhitomin Shul, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 13 & 14, Shpitz Zhitomin and Binyomin Geller, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 17 & 18, Burshteyn Tape 2-3, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 19 & 20, Geller, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 21-22, Goluvinskara, Potina, Zhitomir, Antsis, Kayke, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 23 & 24, Antsis, Tape 2-3, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 25 & 26, Shore, Berdichev, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 27 & 28 Vaysman Berdichev, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 29 & 30, Vaysman Berdichev, Tape 2 and Tsymberl/slaughter Skoblitskii Berdichev, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 31 & 32, Skoblitskii, Berdichev Tape 2-3, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 35 & 36, Grigorii adm Liudmilla Shore, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 37 & 38, Poberevskii Zhmelinka, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 39-40, Poberevskii Zhmelinka Gaykman, Shargood Tour, Vaybman (Box 10)
      - Tape 41 & 42, Vaysman, Shargorod, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 43 & 44, Vaysman, Shargood, Rivels and Vinnitsa Women's Club, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 45 & 46, Beyle, Cherkova, Vinnistsa, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 47 & 48, Beyle Cherkova and Furer, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 49-50, Avrum Furer and Reyze Shvaybish, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 51 & 52, Reyze Shvaybish and Yosel Kogan, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 53 & 54, Yosel Kogan Tulchen, Tape 3, and Moyshe Kuperschmit Bratslav, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 55 & 56, Mayshu Kupershmit, Braslave, Mayte Yerukhman Shargorud, July 2002 (Box 10)
    - May 2003 (Box 10)
      - Tape 57 & 58, Yerukhman and Clara Kurman, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 59 & 60, Clara Kurman Tape 2 and Sheyndele Krasner, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 61 & 62, Sheyndel Krasner, Tape 3-4, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 63 & 64, Mire Murovenaia and Avrum Burshteyn, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 65 & 66, Avrum Burshteyn, Tape 2 and Gayor, Teplik, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 67 & 68, Mashe Yakuta, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 69 & 70, Mashe Yakuta (Box 10)
      - Tape 71 & 72, Tabele Palatnik and Sofiya Palatnik, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 73 & 74, Sofiya Palanik, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 75 & 76, Sheyne Shafir, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 77 & 78, Bershad Street Conversation, Gisya Leterman, and Lyke Bershadskii, July 2002 (Box 10)
    - June 2003 (Box 10)
      - Tape 79 & 80, Leyke Bershadskii, Tape 203, Natfoli Shork, June 2003 (Box 10)
      - Tape 81 & 82, Naftoli Shor Tape 2-3, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 83 & 84, Khayke Yankevna Geventer Khayim and Moti Rubin, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 85 & Tape 86, Khayim and Moti Rubin and Bela Kipnis, July 2002 (Box 10)
      - Tape 87, Bella Kipnis, July 2002 (Box 10)
    - August 2003 (Box 10)
      - Tape 59, Polina Iuris, Fraim Bukhsteyh, Ivano, Frakovsk (Box 10)
      - Tape 60, Fraim Bukasteyh (Box 10)
      - Tape 61, Fraim Bukasteyh (Box 10)
      - Tape 62 & 63, Fraim Bukasteyh and Hersh Katz (Box 10)
      - Tape 64 & 65, Hersh Katz (Box 10)
      - Tape 64 & 65 Hersh Katz, August 2003; (Copy) (Box 10)
      - Tape 66 & 67, Dovid Vider (Box 10)
      - Tape 68 & 69, Dovid Vider and Yosef Greyer (Box 10)
      - Tape 70 & 71, Yozef Grey and Yozef Burg-Chernovtzy (Box 10)
      - Tape 72 & 73, Yozef Burg-Chernovtzy (Box 10)
      - Tape 78 & 79, Shaya Kleiman and Riva Gimelbrandt (Box 10)
      - Tape 80 & 81, Seymon Later (Box 10)
      - Tape 82 & 83, Avrum Gelman (Box 10)
      - Tape 84 & 85, Avrum Gelman and Abram Kaplan (Box 10)
      - Tape 86 & 87, Abram Kaplan and Zhilya Khayut (Box 10)
      - Tape 90 amp; 91, Donna Presler, Rita Shreibysk, and Pinie Goldfeld (Box 10)
    - September 2009 (Box 10)
      - Tape 99 & 100, Raisa Chukh and Efim Skobeitski (Box 10)
      - Tape 101 & 102, Berditchev Tour and Veniamin Geller (Box 10)
      - Tape 103 & 104, Grigory Shraybman and Lazar Burshtein (Box 10)
      - Tape 105 & 106, Lazar Burshtein and Maria Groisburd (Box 10)
      - Tape 107 & 108, Maria Groisburd, Berl Dorfman, and Binyomin Feldman (Box 10)
      - Tape 109 & 110, Binyomin Feldman (Box 10)
      - Tape 111 & 112, Meyshe Stotland and Rachel Feldman (Box 10)
      - Tape 113 & 114, Rachel Felman (Box 10)
    - October 2003 (Box 10)
      - Tape 1 & 2, Tortchinskii (Box 10)
      - Tape 3 & 4, Khandros (Box 10)
      - Tape 5 & 6, Derbaremdiker (Box 10)
      - Tape 7 & 8, Polonne (Box 10)
      - Tape 9 & 10, Goldenber/Zale, Polonnoe (Box 10)
      - Tape 11 & 12, Kleiner (Box 10)
      - Tape 13 & 14, Kleiner, Volynskii, Vertman (Box 10)
      - Tape 17 & 18, Geiller, Izraslav, and Liberzon Slavuta (Box 10)
      - Tape 19 & 20, Liberzon Slavata (Box 10)
      - Tape 21 & 22, Itskhak Tzvi, Vaynashaynboym, Moyshe ben Zalmar (Box 10)
      - Tape 23 & 24, Fish and Rovno, Synagogoue, etc. (Box 10)
      - Tape 25 & 26, Fish, Zoruk Kurlianchik, and Novgarad Volynsky (Box 10)
      - Tape 27 & 28, Kurlianchik, Sorc Litvak (Box 10)
      - Tape 29 & 30, Litvak (Box 10)
      - Tape 31 & 32, Litvak and Shayngart (Box 10)
      - Tape 33 & 34, Kitterman (Box 10)
      - Tape 35 & 36, Shvaytzbroyt and Shvardovskaia (Box 10)
      - Tape 37 & 38, Shvardovskaia (Box 10)
      - Tape 39 & 40, Hirshteyn (Box 10)
      - Tape 43 & 44, Dorfman (Box 10)
      - Tape 45 & 46, Lebvol Zholhva and Dora Weismann (Box 10)
      - Tape 47 & 48, Dora Weismann (Box 10)
      - Tape 49 & 50, Leyber, Lybel, and Weiss Drohobyez (Box 10)
      - Tape 51 & 52, Weiss, Kamerman (Box 10)
      - Tape 53 & 54, Kamerman, Dorfman (Box 10)
      - Tape 57 & 58, Rak Meler (Box 10)
    - -02 Raisa Isakovna (Rokhl) Rusakovskaya, B.1925, Chernobyl, Int. in Kiev, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -03 Raisa Isakovna (Rokhl) Rusakovskaya, B.1925, Chernobyl, Int. in Kiev, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -04 Motl Isasskovich Derbaremdiker B.1920, Berdichev, Int. in Kiev, Synagogue (Galitskaya), Kiev, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -05 Anna Moiseevna Marmalevskaya B.1923, Belaie Tserkov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -05 Anna Moiseevna Marmalevskaya B.1923, Belaie Tserkov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -07 Khariton Berman, Int. in Belaia Tserkov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -08 Khariton Berman, Chaia Yakovlevna Bublitskaia B.1925, Kishinev, Int. in Belaia Tserkov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -09 Chaia Yakovlevna Bublitskaia B.1925, Kishinev, Khariton Berman, Int. in Belaia Tserkov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -10 Tour of Belaia Tserkov with Abram Berman, Road from Belaia Tserkov to Korsun, Tour of Korsun Museum of Regional Association of Jewish shteltls in Ukraine, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -11 Meyshe Ochertiany; B.1929, Korsun, Int. in Korsun at home of Hmiel Belobrov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -12 Shmiel Belobrov B.1929, Korsun, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -13 Shmiel Belobrov B.1929, Korsun, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -14, Korsun city tour (castle), Tseytl (Tsili Davidovna) Kislinskaia, B.1924, Korsun, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -15 Tseytl (Tsili Davidovna) Kislinskaia, B1924, Korsun, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -16 Tsolik Groysman B.1923, Tarashe, Int. in Korsun, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -17 Tsolik Groysman B.1923, Tarashe, Int. in Korsun, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -18 Raisa Teplitskaia B.1930, Ternivke, Int. in Uman, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -19 Uman, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -20 Uman, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -21 Yuri Rafulovich Krasheny B.1912, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -22 Manya (Malke) Waldman B.1936, Uman, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -23 Khayke Gevinter B.1933, Bershad, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -24 Khayke Gevinter B.1933, Bershad, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -25, Musya Moiseevna Vaynshteyn B.1935, Dzhurin, Int. in Nemirov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -26, David Grigorievich Geller B.1929, Zhmerinka, Sofia Abramovna Geller B1929, Bratslav, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -27, David Grigorievich Geller B.1929, Zhmerinka, Sofia Abramovna Geller B1929, Bratslav, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -28 Moyshe Kupershmidt B.1914, Int. in Bratslav, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -29 Moyshe Kupershmidt B.1914, Int. in Bratslav, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -30 Asya Konstantinovna Barshteyn B.1928, Shargood, Int. in Vinnistsa, Road to Yampol, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -31 Anna Borisovna Tkach B.1935, Kleyn Chernovits, Int. in Yampol, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -32 Anna Borisovna Tkach B.1935, Kleyn Chernovits, Int. in Yampol, Ester Khanovna Preger B.1928, Tomashpol, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -34 Klara Naumovna Sapozhnik B.1924, Tomashpol, Dora Bentsionovna Gluzman B.1925, Tomashpol, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -35 Raya Leybovna (Rive) Kazakevich B.1925, Litin, Klara (Khayke) Borisovna Vaynman B.1939, Vinnitsa, Int. in Bar, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -36 Mikhail Abramovich Zhovtis B.1927, Khmelnik, Int. in Bar, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -37 Mikhail Abramovich Zhovtis B.1927, Khmelnik, Int. in Bar, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -38 Izrail Yosifovich Glazer B.1919, Podhaeste, Int. in Ternopil, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -39 Izrail Yosifovich Glazer B.1919, Podhaeste, Int. in Ternopil, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -40 Tour of Kremenits with Larissa Klivch, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -41 Izrail Yosifovich Glazer B.1919, Podhaeste, Int. in Ternopil, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -42 Esya Peysakhivna (Asya Petrovna) Sculova B.1928, Zvil (Novgorod-Volyn.), Int. in Chortkov, Chortkov Memorial, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -43 Chortkov tour- Synagogue, Dovid Vider, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -44 Dovid Vider B.1922, Szeged, Int. in Kolomia, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -45 Kolomia Synagogue, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -46 Kolomia Synagogue, Shloyme (Semyon Semyonovich) Krotsh B.1922, Shtefanesht, Int. in Kolomia, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -47 Shloyme (Semyon Semyonovich) Krotsh B.1922, Shtefanesht, Int. in Kolomia, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -48 Shloyme (Semyon Semyonovich) Krotsh B.1922, Shtefanesht, Int. in Kolomia, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -49 Roman Beleichuk B.1963, Kolomia, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -50 Yosef Groyf B.1922, Kolomia, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -51 Dovid Vider B.1922, Szeged, Int. in Kolomia, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -52 Dovid Vider B.1922, Szeged, Shloyme (Semyon Semyonovich) Krotsh B.1922, Shtefanesht, Int. in Kolomia, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -53 Dovid Vider B.1922, Szeged, Shloyme (Semyon Semyonovich) Krotsh B.1922, Shtefanesht, Int. in Kolomia, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -54 Urn (Aaron) Vikto Kalmanovich Biter B.1918, Popelnike, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -55 Urn (Aaron) Vikto Kalmanovich Biter B.1918, Popelnike, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -56 Dovid Vider B.1922, Szeged, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -57 Moisei Efremovich Pinkasovich B.1946, Vibarov (Novobarova), Int. in Rakhov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -58 Moisei Efremovich Pinkasovich B.1946, Vibarov (Novobarova), Int. in Rakhov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -59 Moisei Efremovich Pinkasovich B.1946, Vibarov (Novobarova), Int. in Rakhov, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -60 Hershl Yulyevich Vider B.1922, Mukachevo, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-13, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-14, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-15, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-16, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-17, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-18, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-19, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-20, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-21, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-22, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-23, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-24, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-25, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-26, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-27, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-28, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-29, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-30, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-31, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-32, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-33, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-34, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-35, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-36, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-37, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-38, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-39, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-40, 2005 (Box 11)
    - -2-01, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-02, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-03, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-04, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-05, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-06, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-07, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-08, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-09, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-10, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-11, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-12, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-13, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-14, 2006 (Box 11)
    - -2-14, 2006 (Box 11)